# **Piotr Moskal**

Product Owner Customer Service Specialist (B2B)

E-mail: for pit@gazeta.pl Tel: +48 602 324 919 City: Kraków, Poland

### LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/piotrmoskal-522baa24/

#### <u>Jira:</u>

https://id.atlassian.com/invite/p/jir a-software? id=yqis3jG8Qiqpe7F6fB1ulA

#### Skills:

Jira

Trello

Confluence

MS Excel – advanced

MS Office, OpenOffice

advanced

Communication tools (Zoom,

Skype, Webex)

**EFI** 

**MyPrint** 

Driving licence (B)

### Language skills:

English – advanced (Business English) Russian – basic

## **Summary:**

Product Owner, Business Engineering Spv and B2B Customer Service Specialist focused on customers' needs and products technical limitations. Skilled in Crisis Management, Critical Thinking and Coaching. Experienced in project teams both as leader and member. Focused on solutions and ensuring no problems are overlooked. Experience in cooperation with customers, other departments and 3<sup>rd</sup> party subcontractors.

## **Experience:**

### Plastcard Jan 2021 - Oct 2021

### **Pricing Specialist**

- Checking bid consistency, clarifying details and customers' expectations, revise technical possibilities
- Pricing, price-lists, creating calculating sheets,
- Creating price-lists for new equipment
- Obtaining offers from subcontractors
- Production coordination: scheduling, transport and production supervision at subcontractors

### Walstead Central Europe (formerly RR Donnelley)

Sep 1998 - May 2019

## **Customer Service Specialist (B2B)**

**Business Engineering Spv**, Estimating and Technology Department since Mar 2000

Many customers' bids were challenging, which meant I needed to cooperate with other departments and 3<sup>rd</sup> party subcontractors. I could processed the bid as an individual project following these steps: checking bid consistency, clarifying details and customers' expectations, revise technical possibilities, looking for solutions in-house, evaluate production paths, searching for subcontractors for parts not possible to produce internally, request prices, collecting data and translating them to the required pricing scheme.

My job required cooperation with customers, different departments and 3rd party subcontractors.

Main responsibilities:

- Processing standard orders: revise customers' orders, keeping up-todate production forecast, preparing product description for production departments, supervision of production steps, negotiating with customers' in case of production problems, preparing mailing and shipment lists, etc, invoicing
- Processing claims
- Advise customers in choosing print options and other special services, production scenarios for standard and non-standard orders, looking for solutions and subcontractors

- Pricing, price-lists, creating calculating sheets, tender documentation
- Assisting sales during meeting with customers
- Job costs analysis before and post-production after sale
- Examine technical limitations of customer's requests, cooperate with sales and customer service to clarify the customer's needs and expectations
- Standard and non-standard products presentations and training for the customers and internal trainings – my presentation has been used by sales, CS and marketing

**Prior experience :** site manager assistant, (ScanNova, Rondo Kotlarskie Tower, Oct 1996 - Nov.1997 – translations, site meetings and tours minutes, querying suppliers and subcontractors)

#### **Hobbies:**

Urban farming — planting
fruits and vegetables in
house, balcony etc.

Kraków — at present mostly
visiting Stronghold
Kraków relicts

Cycling

XX c. music
L'art nouveau, modernism,
Impressionism

### **Education**

Product Owner Bootcamp (60h) - Future Collars
Civil Engineering – Politechnika Krakowska – 4 years
Team Management, Crisis Management, Project Management (incl. Agile and scrum), Supply Chain Management, Design Thinking, Professional Coaching, Excel For Professional, Critical Thinking.

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji oraz przyszłych rekrutacji zgodnie z Rozporządzeniem Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawie ochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawie swobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (RODO).